# **GRANT GLOMSTEAD**

7050 Hatchery Rd, Waterford MI, 48327 gglomstead@comcast.net (248)-410-9059

### Objective

As a student graduating with a master's degree in engineering technology at Wayne State University, I plan on obtaining an interesting job in the Audio/Visual/Broadcast engineering field that will jump-start a long, successful career. Along with years of experience in the IT field, and a degree focusing on media and technology from Michigan State, I plan to use my wide array of skills to succeed in the AV industry.

### Education

Wayne State University Attending as of Spring 2019.

42 W Warren Ave, Detroit, MI 48202 Pursuing a master's in engineering technology.

Michigan State University Graduated in the summer of 2017.

East Lansing, Michigan 48824 Major: B.S. in Media and Information.

Minor: Information and Technology.

### **Work Experience**

#### Marsh and McLennan Agency

03/2018 - Present - Supervisor - AJ Michaud: 989-355-0145

Duties: System Support Specialist for Troy MI office. Imaging computers, managing servers, working in active directory, and general computer maintenance.

#### **Line2Line Coatings**

06/2011 - Present - Supervisor - Andy Suman: 248-310-1850

Duties: Promotional video production, and technical advisor. Works on system security, database management, video surveillance and more.

#### CAS Technology Department at MSU

04/2015 - 08/2017 - Supervisor - Sam Mills: 517-490-1179

Duties: Installing, maintaining, and fixing a wide array of computers and other technology in the Communication, Arts, Sciences building at Michigan State University, which houses over three thousand machines.

#### **Huron Valley Sinai Hospital**

05/2012 - 06/2012 - Supervisor - Deana Brightman

Duties: Internship with Information-Technology Department and other departments such as: Operating Room, Cath Lab, Facilities, and more. Installing and maintaining computer hardware.

## Skills Summary

- Knowledge and experience with web-based languages such as HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP, and SQL, plus other languages such as C++, PLC, Atmel AVR, and Python.
- Certificate in Fanuc Handling Tool Operations, Robot Programming and ROBOGUIDE Simulation Course.
- Skills dealing with implementation, maintenance, and problem solving on all computer operating systems.
- Experience with video/audio production and graphic design.
- Hands on experience with Extron, Textron, and other audio and video components while installing and implementing technology in projects such as the new Spartan Newsroom and Immersive Media/Motion Capture Studio at MSU.